-布罗克  -什么事
- Brock. - Yeah?
住手
Stop!
擅闯我的地盘  你们最好有充分的理由
Better have a damn good reason for trespassing on my land.
如果这是你的地盘
If this is your land,
你一定就是萨尼·克劳
you must be Sani Crow.
我们找切顿·里特斯通
We're looking for Chayton Littlestone.
他杀了我们的朋友  她是个警察
He killed our friend. She was a cop.
那你们这趟算是白费了
Then you came a long way for nothing.
我操  都怪你
Oh, fuck. I blame you for this.
你说切顿杀的那个女人
This woman you say Chayton killed,
她怎么得罪他了
what did she do to him?
没得罪他
Nothing.
那他为什么杀她
Then why would he take her life?
因为他是个变态
'Cause he's a fucking psychopath.
有段时间你们
There was a time when you people
都该管他叫野人
would have called him a wild savage instead.
对  这么叫他没错
Yeah, that sounds about right.
听着  他来寻求你的帮助
Listen, he came to you for help
然后你给他庇护
and you gave him sanctuary.
这我理解  他是你的人
I understand that. He's your people.
但现在方圆一千英里内
But right now every cop
所有警察都在找他
within a thousand miles is looking for him.
这种麻烦你也惹不起吧
Not even you can avoid that kind of heat.
所以我没让他留下
That's why I didn't allow him to stay.
-他什么时候走的  -胡德
- When did he leave? - Hood.
在几天前
A few days before you showed up.
他去哪里了
And where did he go?
最有可能去了法国区那边
My best guess would be the Quarter.
那地方不大
It's not a big place.
我们走
Let's go.
我敢打赌他在说谎
Hundred bucks says he's lying.
-没关系  -为什么
- Doesn't matter. - Why not?
他让我们去法国区
He sent us to the French Quarter.
不管他出卖我们还是切顿
Whether he's selling us out or Chayton,
最终我们都是去那里
we all end up in the same place.
《黑吃黑》第三季 第八集
Banshee S03E08
漂亮
Yeah!
布罗克  你看到他了吗
Brock, do you see him?
我什么都看不到  人太他妈多了
I can't see anything. The crowd's too damn thick.
狠揍那个狗娘养的
Hit that motherfucker.
-狠揍那个狗娘养的  -伙计们  我们来加注
- Hit that motherfucker. - Boys, let's up the ante.
我们来点真格的
Let's get some real shit up in here.
好  好
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
耶
Yeah!
你怎么会到这种鬼地方来
How the hell did you get down there?
女士们先生们  压轴大戏马上开演
Ladies and gentlemen, it is time for our main event.
这方  来自鬼知道是哪里来的
In this corner, from God knows where,
量级...谁他妈管这么多
weighing in at-- who gives a fuck?
我们战无不胜的冠军
Our undefeated champion
屠杀者
the Slayer!
是我鼻子有问题  还是这儿真的臭气熏天
Is it me, or does this entire place smell like ass?
现在
And now,
让我们欢迎大家最喜爱的选手
joining us in a surprise appearance,
在地下搏击场惊艳登场
a favorite here at the Underground.
重生
Born again.
没错
Oh, yeah.
切顿
Chayton!
胡德
Hood.
抱歉  借过
Sorry. Excuse me.
我看不到你  你在哪里
I can't see you. Where are you?
胡德  你在哪里
Hood, where are you?
干掉他
Finish him.
操
Fuck.
胡德  你他妈干嘛呢  胡德
Hood, what the hell are you doing? Hood!
胡德
Hood!
那个女条子
The lady cop,
生前是你的女人
she was your woman?
很好
Good.
不许动  切顿
Don't move, Chayton.
去你的吧  条子
Fuck you, cop.
我下一枪会轰掉你的脑袋
The next shot will blow your fucking face off.
这里不许带枪
There are no guns allowed in here.
我们是警察  混蛋
We're cops, asshole.
这个人因涉嫌谋杀被通缉
This man is wanted for murder.
这里不一样  在这里  他受我保护
Not here, he's not. Here, that man is under my protection.
好  那我也崩了你
Fine. I'll shoot you, too.
这招不错
Now that'd be a neat trick.
跟计划不一样啊
This didn't go as planned.
-切顿  -操
-Chayton. - Fuck.
跟你打的这人也是个条子吗
Is that man you're fighting also a pig?
是
Yes.
虽然我很乐意
Now, as much as I'd love
让这些粉丝们得偿所愿  观赏死亡
to give these fans the death they deserve,
但恐怕杀死警官
I think that killing a police officer
会使我和执法部门的关系复杂化
might complicate my arrangement with local law enforcement.
够了
You're done.
够了  切顿
You're done, Chayton!
改日再会  条子
I'll see you again, cop.
还他妈用你说
Yeah, you fucking know you will.
先生们  你们要知道
Now, what you gentlemen need to understand
切顿在地下搏击场
is that Chyton is a beloved figure here
深受欢迎
at the Underground.
你现在还没被这些狂热的粉丝们
And it is only my goodwill
碎尸万段
that is keeping these dedicated fans
全靠的是我的善心
from tearing you apart limb from limb.
我打赌
And I'll wager you,
趁着我的善心还在
you got roughly 60 seconds
你能有大概六十秒时间
before that goodwill fails me.
现在开始
Starting now.
来  走  咱们快出去
Come on, let's go. Let's get the hell out.
来
Come on.
该死  我还以为任务就是盯着切顿呢
God damn it, I thought the plan was to watch Chayton.
我不想再次放掉他
I didn't want to lose him again.
我确定一定以及肯定他刚刚已经走了
I'm pretty sure that's what just happened.
-现在他知道我们来了  -这说法算温和的了
- Now he knows we're here. - That's an understatement.
他要是离开新奥尔良怎么办
What if he leaves New Orleans?
他哪也去不了
He's not going anywhere.
博登  怎么了
What is it, Burton?
我们在工厂对货品清单有一点小分歧
There's a small discrepancy in inventory at the factory.
-怎么  货少了  -正相反
- What, missing product? - The opposite.
我们的利润貌似比销售要多
It seems we're showing more profit than sales.
这倒是个不错的问题
Well, that's a good problem to have.
您想让我怎么做
What would you like me to do?
调查一下
Look into it.
告诉我你查到什么
Tell me what you find out.
还有事吗
Anything else?
没了  就这事
No. Nothing else.
博登看起来有点忧心忡忡的
Burton looked worried.
博登一直都那副样子
Oh, Burton always looks worried.
生意上的事罢了
It's just business.
我以为你出去了
Hey, I thought you went out.
你想错了  又一次
You thought wrong, again.
你丢了什么东西吗
Did you lose something?
不是东西  十二万五千美金
Not something. $125,000.
很明显  有人不知道
Apparently some motherfucker
我还会数数
forgot I'm the one who can count.
你是怎么想的  要拿这些钱
What the fuck were you thinking taking that money?
打住
Now hold on.
比起我现在的麻烦  这只是小事一桩
It's just a small taste of what I got coming to me.
在我们想出解决办法之前  这都不算事
Nothing coming to no one until we all decide how to handle it.
我又不是要跑路去大西洋城
It's not like I'm running off to Atlantic City.
我可不是傻子
I'm not an idiot.
你看起来就像一个傻子
You doing a damn good impression of one.
我遇到点事
Something came up.
-什么事  -私人的事
- What? - Something personal.
你知道这么多就够了
That's all you need to know.
喂  你要去哪
Hey. Hey!
别管了  贾伯
Let it go, Job.
我可不是为了替你收拾烂摊子的
I ain't sitting on this just to cover for your fat ass.
你听明白没
You hear me?
做你该做的
You do what you got to do.
我也是
So will I.
直接把包带去交易点
Take the bag directly to the drop point.
只能把包给莫拉莱斯本人
You deliver to Morales himself or no one at all.
-记住了吗  -记住了
- Okay? - Yes, ma'am.
有问题吗
Is there a problem?
如果你叔叔发现了
If your uncle finds out...
有些机会是要抓住的
Some chances are worth taking.
你难道不这么认为吗
Don't you think?
是的  女士
Yes, ma'am.
完事之后打电话给我
Call me when you're finished.
你违反了我们跟弗拉奇尔的协议
You're violating our agreement with Frazier
把货卖给了萨尔瓦多人
and selling to the Salvadorans.
没错
Yes.
你叔叔不会允许的
Your uncle won't like that.
那就别告诉他
Then don't tell him.
把这当做我们的秘密
It can be our secret.
到最后
And in the end...
他会因此感谢我们的
he'll thank us for it.
我不会告诉他的
I'm not going to tell him.
应该由你来说
It should come from you.
我是想要帮他
I'm trying to help him.
你难道看不出吗
Can't you see that?
这个女人让他变得软弱
This woman is making him weak.
他正在做出错误的决定
He's making bad decisions.
把从前的成果全都拿来冒险
He's risking everything he's built.
不会这样的
That's not going to happen.
已经这样了
It's already happening.
好吧
Fine.
做你想做的
Do what you have to do.
不过提醒你  你这是逼他在我们之中选一个
But just know you'll be making him pick between us.
你真的觉得
And do you really think
他会选你
he'll choose you
而不是他特别的侄女
over his very special niece?
再来一次  很好
Again. Good, good.
很好  一二三  躲
That's it. One, two, three, slip.
好样的  宝贝
There you go, baby.
上勾拳  上勾拳  一二三四
Uppercuts, uppercuts-- one, two, three, four, five,
二二三四
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
没错  一二三  躲
That's it. One, two, three, slip.
保持  头抬起来  抬起来
Stay-- keep your head up. Keep your head up.
一二三  躲  一二三  躲
One, two, three, slip. One, two, three, slip.
-奥斯卡  -沙格
- Oscar. - Shug.
你在这干什么
What are you doing here?
他怎么样
How's he doing?
从各方面来看  他还挺不错的
He was doing good, all things considered.
不过几个月前还挺糟糕的  你知道吗
But a few months back, things got bad, you know?
天天跟医生护士打交道
Between the doctors, the nurses,
不停地换新药
all the new prescriptions,
压得我们喘不过气来  沙格
We're drowning, Shug.
打开
Open it.
天呐
Jesus.
不  这太多了
No, this is way too much.
我欠你父亲的可比这些多多了
It's not even close to what I owe your old man.
听着  爸爸只是像所有其他拳击手一样
Look, Pop took his chances just like every other boxer
上场搏命罢了
that climbs into that ring.
当时倒下的说不定也会是你
Could have just as easily been you.
不是的
It wasn't.
你要不四处看看吧
Why don't you stick around, you know?
你可以指点指点这些毛头小子
You could give some of those young punks
传授你的智慧
the benefit of your wisdom.
这个袋子就是我所有的智慧所在
That bag is about all the wisdom I got left.
你想把我吓出心脏病吗
You trying to give me a heart attack?
求之不得
A girl can dream.
说吧
Start talking.
不
No.
你一点都不幼稚  贾伯
That's real mature, Job.
现在你告诉我
Now you tell me
你他妈到底把钱给谁了
who did you give that motherfucking money to?
他叫小奥斯卡·克鲁兹
His name is Oscar Cruz, Jr.
他父亲曾经是拳击手
His father was a fighter.
所以呢  你是忘记给他儿子送成年礼吗
So, what, you forgot his son's bar mitzvah present?
西尼尔当时并未做好上场的准备
Senior wasn't ready for that fight.
但主办方不在乎
The promoters didn't care.
我也不在乎
I didn't care either.
箭在弦上不得不发
I mean, the title was on the line.
我下了几次重手后
The ref should have stopped
裁判应该马上叫停比赛的
the fight after I landed a few big ones.
天知道我控制不住了
Lord knows I couldn't.
他的头撞到围栏上前
By the time his head hit that canvas,
我对他脑子猛击了好几下
I had scrambled his brains so badly
以至于他后来再也没法说话了
that he would never speak again.
那他现在在哪
So where is he now?
他住在西部某家奇贵无比的疗养院里
He's in some overpriced nursing home out West.
流着口水  穿着尿布
Drooling and wearing a diaper.
现在你能把
Now, could you please
分电盖还给我吗
give me my distributor cap back?
有人在吗
Is anyone there?
看起来你在这被关了很久了
Oh, looks like you've been down here quite some time.
他们好像把你整得很惨
They worked you over real good.
永远未雨绸缪
Always be prepared.
别担心  我不会伤害你的
Don't worry. I'm not gonna hurt you.
我不会伤害你  我给你松开
I'm not gonna hurt you. I'll cut you loose.
慢慢来
Just take your time.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
走吧
Let's go.
留了一个人给你
I saved one for you.
来吧  我们走
Come on, let's go.
有什么事吗
Can I help you?
我要帮你变成更好的人
I am going to help you become a better man.
你到底在说什么
What the fuck are you talking about?
他跟你说了什么
What did he tell you?
你要有风度地把他给你的钱还回去
You are going to graciously return all the money he gave you.
那钱是给我父亲的
That money was a gift to my father.
老奥斯卡·克鲁兹  2007年11月逝世
Oscar Cruz, Sr., died in November of 2007.
我见过你伪造的
I saw your handiwork with the forged
医院表格和保险记录
hospital forms and insurance records.
他儿子已经冒领他的福利多年
Junior's been collecting his benefits for years.
也差不多玩了你这么多年
Almost as long as he's been playing you.
糖果以为我根本不知道
Sugar thinks I have no clue
那晚比赛时发生的事
what really happened in the fight that night.
但我清楚他那样对我父亲
But I know what he did
根本不是因为拳击比赛
to my father had nothing to do with boxing.
他夺走了一切...
He took everything...
混蛋  我不是来听你叨叨的
Bitch, I ain't come to hear your sob story.
我来拿钱
I come for the money.
那就自己来拿
Then come and take it.
不管你过去做了什么都不关我的事
What you did or did not do in the past don't mean shit to me.
我关心的是此时此刻
What concerns me is a colleague
我的同伴不能按他妈的计划行事
that can't keep to the motherfucking plan in the here and now.
你要记住
I just want you to remember
我给过你这个混蛋机会
I gave your punk ass a chance.
要像蝴蝶一样灵巧  兔崽子
Float like a butterfly, motherfucker.
你自以为知道事实  贾伯
You think you know what happened, Job,
但并非如此
but you don't.
她是谁
Who was she?
如果既不为钱又不为名
Well, if it ain't for money and it ain't for glory,
那只剩一个可能了
there's only one thing left.
那个女人是谁
Who was she?
她叫瓦内萨
Her name was Vanessa.
我爱她  但是她爱着他
I loved her, but she loved him.
我能听到她在人群中为她的男人欢呼雀跃
I could hear her in the stands cheering for her man.
但那个人不是我
A man who wasn't me.
我觉得非常痛苦
I never felt that kind of pain.
我不知道如何是好
I didn't know what to do with it.
所以我让奥斯卡来处理
So I gave it to Oscar to deal with instead.
25年来
For 25 years,
我把节省下来的都给了他们家
I sent his family anything I could spare.
虽然不多  但是我的心意
Wasn't much, but it was something.
听我说  放下吧
Listen to me. Let it go.
我听这些悲悲切切的事
I have had more than my fair share
听得够多了
of Podunk Tragedy Theater.
我没那么多精力
I do not have the energy.
等等
Hey.
你可以留着这些钱的
You could have kept that money, you know.
完全不用跟我打招呼
Didn't have to say a damn word to me.
为什么还回来
So why'd you give it back?
我并没有全还给你啊
I didn't give it all back.
*你的爱就是一剂猛药*
* Your love ain't never been so strong *
*十六只蜡烛正燃烧*
* 16 candles burning *
*缠绵整夜到破晓*
* Make love all night long *
*爱是*
* Love is *
*两条河流并排流淌*
* Two rivers running side by side *
*爱是*
* Love is *
*两条河流并排流淌*
* Two rivers running side by side *
这里没一个人肯跟我们说话
Ain't nobody in here gonna talk to us.
是啊
No.
但他们会和切顿说话
But they'll talk to Chayton.
等他来找我们吗
And he'll find us?
我是这么想的
That's the idea.
胡德
You know, Hood,
我们共事时间也不短了
we've been working together for a while now
可我发现
and I realized
我根本不了解你
I don't know the first thing about you.
比如  你是哪里人
You know, like where you're from.
你老家
Originally.
满街都是大白天就喝酒的人
Town full of day drinkers.
看得出他们...
That's a concept I can get--
你有什么心事吗  布罗克
You got something on your mind, Brock?
好像有吧
Yeah, I guess I do.
你看
You know,
我们
when we--
我们杀了本渡后
when we killed Hondo,
我就发誓再也不杀人了
I swore to myself never again.
可我现在
And yet here I am
才没过多久
a short while later
就又来跟你杀人了
on another assassination junket.
有时法律无法给人正义还人公道
Sometimes the law can't give justice.
别欺骗自己了  胡德
Oh, don't kid yourself, Hood.
这不是正义
This isn't justice.
杀本渡也不是正义
Hondo wasn't justice, okay?
这只是冰冷残酷而又自私的报复
This is cold, hard, self-serving revenge.
我们是杀人犯  别欺骗自己了
We're killers, okay? Don't make us idiots.
他妈的声音轻点
Keep your fucking voice down.
管他们干什么  全都是醉鬼
Who gives a shit? They're all drunk.
-你得冷静  -去他妈的
- You need to calm down. - Fuck that, man.
我们开车横跨五州到这就为了杀一个人
We drove through five states to come here to kill a man.
你不必杀人
You don't have to kill anyone.
那我来这里干什么
Then what the hell am I doing here?
我来这里干什么
Huh? What am I doing here?
胡德
Hood!
好爽啊
Oh, my God.
爽死我了
Oh, fuck.
你杀不了我  条子
You can't kill me, cop.
你只是凡人
You're just a man.
没人能杀死我
No man can kill me.
胡德
Hood!
靠  快给我
Damn it, give me that.
新奥尔良港
我低估了你
I underestimated you.
你不是警察
You're not a cop.
没错
No.
你们总是生活在谎言中
Your people deal in lies.
你永远不会理解
You will never understand
真正目标的纯洁性
the purity of true purpose.
精神召唤的纯洁性
Of a spiritual calling.
你什么都不是
You're nothing.
我是名勇士
I am a warrior.
我就是用这双手掐住她的脖子
I held her neck in these hands.
那么的纤弱
So delicate.
我的指尖可以感受到她跳动的脉搏
Felt her pulse tapping against my fingertips.
感受到她的生命
The life running through her.
趁当地警察还没赶来  我们应该
We should probably get the hell out of Dodge
赶紧离开这里
before the locals show up, huh?
胡德  我们走
Hood, let's go.
我不能回去了
I can't go back.
你说什么
What?
我要做的都做完了
I'm done.
那没有什么让我留恋的了
I got nothing left.
所以就这样了
So that's it?
你就打算这么离开吗
You're just gonna walk away?
为了弄明白你是什么人
You know, I've been driving myself crazy
我快把自己逼疯了  但是够了
trying to figure you out, but I'm done.
你现在是谁  原来是谁
Who you are, who you were,
从什么地方来  我都不在乎
where you're from, I don't care.
我现在都不在乎了
I don't care anymore.
我唯一在乎的是我的小镇
The only thing I care about is my town.
凯·普罗斯特用他的方式控制我们
Kai Proctor has been having his way with us,
控制我们所有人太久了
all of us, for way too long.
但是你
But you,
你是唯一一个那个混蛋控制不了的人
you're the first guy that bastard couldn't own.
你和我一起  我们可以把他彻底扳倒
And together, you and me, we could take him down for good.
不感兴趣
No.
真见鬼
God damn it.
你觉得她想要的是什么
What do you think she would have wanted, huh?
我不会一个人回女妖镇的
I'm not going back to Banshee without you.
你要打完这场战争
Gotta finish what you started.
就算拖我也要亲自把你拖回去
Even if I've got to kick your ass all the way back there myself.
我不会一个人离开的
I'm not leaving without you.
你说完了吗
Are you done?
说完了
I think so.
那走吧
Come on.
以主和教会的名义
In the name of the Lord and the Church,
我们向你伸出信徒之手
we extend to you the hand of fellowship.
我为了自己的缘故而清楚你们的罪行
"I am He who blots out your transgressions for my own sake
出自以赛亚书
忘却你们的罪行
and remembers your sins no more."
请起身  从此你就是教会忠实的一员
Rise up and be ye a faithful member of the Church.
年轻时我们学习
In youth we learn.
年长时我们懂得
In age we understand.
这个是你妈妈留下的
This belonged to your mother.
谢谢你  父亲
Thank you, Father.
谢谢你
Thank you.
凯
Kai.
我们走
Let's go.
迈尔斯餐厅
培根汉堡  芝士汉堡
Bacon burger. Cheeseburger.
我还以为你和那个当兵的结束了呢
I thought you and soldier boy were done.
我们是结束了
We are.
他知道吗
Does he know that?
你好  卡莉
Hello, Carrie.
天哪  你怎么了
Jesus. What happened to you?
我被打劫了
I got robbed.
道格  你没事吧
Doug, are you okay?
我会没事的
I will be.
你报警了吗
Did you call the cops?
没  我自己处理
No, I'll be handling this myself.
也许你能帮我
Maybe you can help.
我知道你父亲对违法犯罪不陌生
I understand your father was no stranger to illegal behavior.
也许你能指点我犯罪心理的玄妙之处
Maybe you could shed some light on the nuances of the criminal mind.
我跟我父亲的关系很复杂
My father and I had a complicated relationship.
我恐怕帮不上什么忙
I doubt I'd be much help.
好吧
Okay.
请再给我倒点水
I'd like some more water, please.
没问题
Of course.
他们从旧作业隧洞进入
They came in through the old service tunnel.
用绞车来突破钢门
A winch was used to breach the steel door.
他们控制了监控摄像机和运动传感器
They took control of the security cameras and motion sensors.
这些人利用了我们的防御系统
These guys used our own defenses to their advantage.
利用立体复制模具和高端复制声音发生器
The biometric lock was bypassed using a dimensional latent clone
破解了生物识别电子锁
and high-end vocal replication generator.
有人近到可以窃取你的声音和指纹
Somebody got close enough to steal your voice and fingerprints.
他们进入以后  旋转保险库密码
Once they were inside, the rolling vault codes
被一个高端黑客破解
were exploited by an elite hacker.
接下来  只需一个有经验的破箱人
After that, all they needed was an experienced safecracker.
就这样  我们的钱成了他们的
And just like that, our money was theirs.
墨菲上校  未知嫌疑人有三个
Captain Murphy, we have three unknowns.
加上开车的就是四个
Van driver makes four.
先说黑客
Start with the hacker.
他破解了我设的每个密码
He defeated every encryption I set up,
避开了每个恶意软件陷阱
avoided every malware trap.
这还不止
And beyond that,
他还黑进了坚不可摧的主机把我们关在外
he hacked into an ironclad mainframe to shut us down.
你是说他跟你一样厉害吗
You're saying he's as good as you?
我是说他更厉害
I'm saying he's better.
说说这个破箱人
Tell me about the safecracker.
锁从死点钻开
The lock was drilled dead center,
换向齿轮被轻易操纵
the tumblers manipulated with a gentle touch.
方法简单  优雅
The approach was simple, elegant.
专业人士的手法
The work of a professional.
你确定不要别的了吗
Are you sure I can't get you anything else?
今天不要了
Not today.
我没弄懂的是你在隧道里对战的那人
The one I haven't figured out is the one you fought in the tunnel.
他受过很好的训练
He was well trained.
致命  但有点生疏了
Lethal, but a little rusty.
他让他的对手活着
He allowed his enemy to live
而不是割了对方的喉咙
instead of cutting his throat.
说明他变心软了
It shows he's gone soft.
也许是有良心了
Maybe grown a conscience.
为什么他的同伴在他撤出之前就炸隧道了
Why have his partners blow the tunnel before he was clear?
忠诚  愿为目标献身
Loyalty and a commitment to the objective.
三号人物会有挑战
Number three is gonna be a challenge.
解散所有士兵
Dismiss all enlisted personnel.
我要他们一小时内离开基地
I want them off the base within the hour.
是的  长官
Yes, sir.
通知总部从今天开始
Notify HQ that as of today
热那亚基地正式关闭
Camp Genoa is officially shut down.
我们要抓到他们并且拿回属于我们的东西
We're gonna hunt them down and take back what they stole from us.
然后我们要让他们付出代价
And then we will make them pay.